First, we'll have the implication by Reverend of Olsink because we're
churners, Mary, to the way that we are.
Let us pray.
Holy Lord, we thank you for gathering us together for this meeting, help us to
set aside the troubles of the day that we carried with us to this place, so we can
be present to one another and to you.
We seek your blessing as we share ideas, progress and accomplishments, and go about doing
the work you've called us to do.
You've charged us with being your hands and feet here on earth for seeing opportunities
in many circumstances, both big and small.
So please reveal to us through our discussion and decisions what you would have us do.
If we have differences, help us to resolve those in a manner that leaves everyone's dignity
in place and with a solution that brings light into our community.
We must have the strength to carry out your mission, your mission of love, justice, peace and
gratitude, and always in the interest of our community and our homes.
We ask this in the name of your son, our Savior, Jesus Christ.
Amen.
Thank you for joining us today, we are going to do this to the light of the United States of America.
And to the Republic for which it stands, one nation, another God, in which it is the will,
with liberty and justice, so we're off.
Four, public input, let's go to personal peer access.
We have that.
Five, plain blists, close to a proof, second.
Parker.
Thank you.
Hi.
Thanks.
Budget amendment number 25-08, receiving and expanding overtime money for work done on the
mama housing authority on the non-tropes tower project and receiving and expanding insurance funds
to repair a 2023 Chevy pickup damage in a wreck on the turn bike.
Yes, it's Jennifer.
It's not here.
I will take this.
I'll leave on this and stay in training questions.
So I'd like to bless it.
This is where we did some work for the mama housing authority and the assets do after hours of
this reimbursement.
Our overtime and then the second one was the insurance check that we got for the
truck that we had the accident on the turn bike in.
So, you know, we get the money because in our revenues and then we're just nursing it back
out.
Most proof.
Sorry.
Parker.
Thank you.
Good evening.
Legal is urged us to make a distinction between the city and the utility side.
Different to do that.
We went out to two different local vendors here and they came up with with L.O. group if you like.
But it could be used on equipment, our uniforms, letter-end, etc. stuff like that.
So this kind of rough the idea of we want to look at rebranding after this or go with this
just for the MSU Bay because I have sounds so I'm like a G-to-brand or you know something
like that.
I agree that over all the women.
So I guess I'll say, I would love to say this rebrand from the, I just, it's kind of bland.
I'd like to say this new several different.
I don't want to say this a lot of money to do something different because we've got streets to do
and everything else so I don't know if we have, I don't know if we have, I don't know if we have.
I don't know if you have to fix the, I just use chat to you, but that's my opinion.
I'd like for us to look at rebranding totally but of course on others, I think it's expensive that
and I don't really want to keep that as low as possible but the emails have been thought.
I feel like the intent of this design here is just to be visible, right?
Like when you see it on a truck or you see it on a shirt, that's the intent, right?
Or let her head, you know, I think those have been a very big, we have separation of the city and the MSV.
That's, that's what I see in here.
I mean, I'm with you, it's kind of plain and I don't have this with any of that one.
Oh, I've got a bit of thinking about it.
Oh, I got to rebrand it totally for a while but it's expensive.
Besides blessing, this is something that I actually learned last week and I've been here 12 years
and so blessed on answer this is maybe on the board and I know what that line is and at the end.
Yeah, I remember.
I did not tell.
I did not tell you that.
No, no.
He's an engineer.
He's how they did.
And that was the, and the design, that's what they came up with, so it's pretty cool.
It is cool.
This logo that you guys have, is that one that you guys, or like you guys like this is the one that we won?
Or maybe they looked at other options.
We looked at lots of options.
Like, do you like it?
Do you like it?
But you're the...
You want to do what you want to do?
What do I see going around back there?
I saw some stuff.
See that?
Yeah.
You can approach the bench.
I want to say it.
I'm just trying to say it.
Well, chat GPT.
Yeah, you can tell because there's words that are misspelled.
Yeah.
Oh, yeah.
That's way out there.
Did you do that?
Which one of you like fondness?
We're just, you know, we're starting.
Right.
Did you see that one?
Sure.
That one that you just said.
Well, it's an image of it.
Yeah.
Right.
It's an object.
Oh, right.
And this one, these are just pretty much your IVs here.
I go back to the one with the state.
And why I got like that?
Maybe have something up in the corner.
Go to now.
Yeah.
What's the pattern?
Well, Jenny, there isn't a disaster.
Jenny was thinking, how are we going to reach the promise?
Hmm.
And I said, I'm not allowed.
I think about that.
Yeah.
We've just stayed with the basic wine.
I mean, because it is Tulsa, just ready to do all back.
It's pretty expensive.
Well, it's same like, but I mean, they're separate still.
Well, if I like this, I'm kind of, I like,
Ooh.
Yeah.
In the face, razzle, dazzle.
But if you guys like it, then it's your...
We can always put blank around it.
But it's a beautiful mess.
Thank you. Thank you.
Yeah, ready?
Yeah.
But then we got a bunch of guys down there wearing that's yeah, that'll happen
I mean if you guys have looked at everything and you like me this this can be yours and that we can still
rebrand this I
Mean but they may not be an expense. We want to go into right now for this
But I'll make emotions to prove this
Hey Parker
Duckel. Hi. E step and Barnes. I
Hey, rat by sawed waste charge agreement
Template authorized the trust manager or as does need to sign the agreement
So it appears in the past we
had
ineffective
System of people charging
They're definitely materials off at the solid waste sign and
Finance was wanting to
Rain in the the process a little bit because there's
We don't believe that people are paying for all that they've dumped out there yet worse than paying for to haul it on
So the just of what this agreement would be it's for businesses
It's not for residential
folks
But they can if they want to
Where they're wanting to charge when they're making a deposit they can set up a charge account agreement
Basically this provides there's two ways that they can do it and it's their choice of how they want to do it
one is that it's they give us a list of
Specific people
There are authorized to
dump in their name and only those people will be able to do it and they have to sign the receipt when they do it
Other option if they don't know who all is going to be taking materials out there in their names
They can open and open a account
But basically they're responsible for everybody that makes the deposit out there in their name that would be an easier thing for them to do
But they have a greater potential liability if somebody goes with the approved list of account in instead of
Employee going out there is the employees brother-in-law that goes out there. They're not authorized to do it and so they can't even though it may really
their staff off saying, I'm depositing for Jane and Park. So, but it's their option is to
which way they want to go. We kicked around various ways that it can still be controlled and
this was the best that we were able to come up with. So I'm assuming you're having people saying,
we didn't up this, where do you get this from? Well, and the tickets have got lost, and so we never
charged anybody for them. This is just a streamlined process of how businesses can deposit there.
In what you're given, and the packet is the list, all the customers that we have. You know,
the more thing in large use, it's customers that have people that come in. So the only way we track
this is by paper tickets. Apparently, that's the way we've done it in the past and not necessarily
signed by anybody. So it's kind of the open account concept. But we've had people complaining,
they didn't authorize something to make that dump. It's just been very loose out there, and in addition
to just losing money on who pays, losing even more money when people don't pay. When, I mean, this
is the idea here. We'd better to have like an iPad. They punch in and who did it and put it right in that
way and stuff on a paper ticket that we lose. That way goes into the system. I think there's a lot of things
we could do. Because I mean, I think we need to look at next year doing, like when you go to a rock or where
they print you out and take it, you know, based off the scales, we just hand right amount. I think there's a lot
of things that could be of it. Yeah, the mechanism of recording it definitely needs to be improved,
but this specific issue is, how are we going to regulate who's depositing on somebody else's account?
Because that happens all the time. And so many people get up some pretty high bills, which are not
they always pay us, but it's just good to have it in a writing, like we have to have a contract with
the insurance firm. And it's only if they want, I mean, they don't have to have it, but then they
have to pay cash when they come out. It's convenience for them. It's full of stuff.
I think the having an approved list is probably the way to go.
I mean that's how it works at like A-S hardware.
This is like that.
Like if I work someplace and I'm they have to call and authorize me to be able to charge things at A-S.
Shouldn't be any different than what you think.
Well that's my opinion.
I mean I definitely.
Yeah.
Well that way if you have a system.
You pull the whole iPad that shows how everybody's authorizes them out there.
And that you're still going to begin to tell you who is authorize.
Yes.
That's the only point in this.
That gives in that opportunity.
And it can all be put on a computer.
Sure.
Yeah.
But it's on then to keep that list current.
Right.
And if they're not on there, then charge them cash.
Correct.
Or whatever.
Yeah.
The problem is if they don't keep it current,
then somebody that is on their list that no longer works for them could still come out there and deposit stuff.
But that's the point.
It's on then to keep that list current.
Yep.
Second.
Parker.
Hi.
Thank you.
And part-time.
And more cooperation.
Number seven with own formerly energy engineering for design and water treatment.
Plant piping motor and pump rehab.
Not to exceed 110,000.
There.
So this is Derek and I.
This is for our water plant and our operations center.
So we know we start now.
I'm like excited.
We sort of replace in our associations.
We need to.
Our water side.
In dust.
And when he was there, looked at it.
We didn't share them.
I mean, some of the.
I mean, like you don't want to touch because.
I mean, you're scared that it be touched.
Then.
Not that it replaced.
So I mean.
This is what we had some positive stuff that.
They've needed some work and we got some quotes on some of that stuff.
I think one pump.
We have.
And we're okay right at the moment.
We got a couple of wells back up on the.
Those're that pump itself.
I said it off.
And they couldn't even.
They make the parts for me.
They're actually going to have to machine the cart out.
To make them.
That's what drove the costs of it.
It was just.
You would.
It would be cheaper actually if I knew.
So that.
Kind of would start it down this room.
right this and make sure that the city is good to allow the water for our citizens.
If we design a new water plant, can we design it that doesn't take $30,000 motors?
Well, that would be a fun.
Sorry, punks.
That's what we talked about, so we're actually going to have the same size motors.
Yeah.
So we don't have any different sizes.
Right.
Because you ever have the one on the shelf that you have and they'll actually have it run
off the FD.
So you know, you'll both speed on first load it down.
There you go.
Yeah.
There will put it on our skates, that's enough so we can watch it from home, we can watch it.
You know, anywhere, it's so much of the electric system, how are you doing?
Perfect.
How many of these we have?
We're going to have to do this.
I'm assuming this is our first one, right?
Well, this would be, well, this would be all of them at there, so they'd be designing the whole
thing inside there.
There's currently there was seven pumps inside there and they're all different sizes, depending
on how much water we need to produce at that moment in time, and you could kick on different
pumps to get different amounts of water.
This would, the idea here would be that we would drop the number that we have there, like
Tyler said, we'd use VFDs to change how fast those pumps are running, that way we can match
what we need to go out.
Thanks for that, right?
So, but there's a pump, there's water towers or anything, but it's just a bit of a bit of a smaller
slayer, you know.
I mean, so is this something we're going to do at all of these sites eventually?
No, I mean.
So this would just be at down at the OPC, there are wells and there's pumps at some of the wells
sites themselves, but this, a lot of our raw water comes to the OPC, we treated that
clear well and then we pump it back out into the system to get rid of the system, and I don't
know the system.
So that's what we're doing is where that comes to the OPC to get treated, is the pumps that are
pumping that back out to the system, and then it'd be that main line actually to come down
to do the feeds back to good rich basically.
We just bought a new pump last year or two, or two years ago, did we get out of the
room street?
Yeah, that was a little, yeah, that was a little.
So, I mean, it's a cool thing, I mean, you know, it's like it's investing in infrastructure
and through things.
We have this hundred and ten thousand dollars budgeted for this thing, for this thing, our
personal service is better at which we can manage to do it.
All right, I'm making motion.
We approve.
Second.
Parker.
Hi.
Donkel.
East up.
And Barton.
Tim, another new business of any of which the business is supposed to be this agenda, and the next one,
11 staff reports, pro trustee community announcements, 13.
This may will be continued from council chambers to be in the staff rooms and purpose of
executive session at the completion of the regular meeting of the Minor City Council.